BGM
It's time for another episode of upcami, this time with Sakura Oda from Morning Musume。 24 and Rio Kitagawa from Morning Musume。 24.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
Now then, let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at our two MCs.
I'm Sakura Oda, and this is a story about my junior colleague, Ako Yumigita.
She loves me so much that she wants to keep a distance from me, and when I talk to her, she basically says yes.
She loves me and wants to keep her distance from me, but this is the first time we've had a disagreement.
On the radio, we talked about whether she wanted to be a beautiful warrior or a princess, and Ako-chan said she wanted to be a princess, and what she envisioned was a princess like the ones in the picture books.
But I'm not a princess... because a princess must have peace.
Who's going to create peace?
I told her she should be a Japanese princess, and she said something like, “I'll be a Japanese princess.
I felt like I should treat her like a 10-year-old sister.
I thought I should treat her like a 10-year-old sister.
I'm sorry, Ako-chan.
I'm Kitagawa, and there's a documentary about Nippon Budokan on Hulu, and this is the story of it
It was my first narration job, but I've never done a job where I only did the voice, so I had to work on the script to get it just right.
It was very difficult because I had to work with the script and the emotions, but one thing that was interesting was that
But one thing that was interesting was that in the first scene in the 17th season, it was written in the script that I was to be called Getter and Haru-san, but when I was asked what I was usually called, I said, “Haru-chan”.
I said, “Haru-chan,” and he said, “Haru-chan,” and then he said, “Getter and Haru-chan in the 17th term.
Haru-chan, even though it's a bit serious.
Yes, it was very interesting to see how you were able to make the market more interesting.
I'm sure that every time I do something new, I'm always impressed by how professional people in this field are.
I'm going to try my best to live the experience I've had in the past, so let's start with this one.
Juice Juice Aiko Dance Lesson
Let's take a look at the dance lesson of Aiko from the latest single of Juice Juice!
Here we go. Ready, go!
Five, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Nine. Ten.
Oh, sorry.
Just the two of us here.
Can you stay in the middle as long as you can? If we go together, we'll end up on top of each other.
So we're gonna have to be a little bit bigger than the people in front.
One more time. Ready?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Let's all take an A here.
A, whatever you want, easy accent. A Any easy to do accent
Five, six, seven, eight.
Zutta zutta zutta
Kita tuttattica
5,6,7,8
1&2&3&4
The position of this one.
I don't want to have two complete rows. I want to have a little separation between this group and that group.
It's a bit of a muehnese thing.
Here we go. Ready.
One, two, three.
Five, six, seven.
Mm-hm-hm-hm.
Yeah, yeah. I'll do that.
So, there's a snapshot of the move here.
Seen.
2, DAC Tonight
DAC promet
Tonight
4,5,6,7
8,1234567
8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15,16,17,18
Oh, sorry! If you guys aren't singing, let's just break for four.
I'm waiting... four with rhythm.
Yes!
Here we go.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap.
Tap-tap-tap-tap-tap-tap-tap-tap-tap-tap-tap-tap-tap-tap-tap-tap. 5, 6.
7 8 1 & 2 & 3 & 4 & cuttacut cuttacut
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
5,6,7,8
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8
2,3,4,5,6,7,8
Tattoo
Exercise bread Exercise bread
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
5 Rhythm
All the way
2,3,4,5,6
2,3,4,5,6,7,8
please.
Thank you for your time.
You must be so relieved.
relieved.
You know.
Enjoy it.
I hate you.
Up the stairs.
Listen to this.
I'm having fun
I was flabbergasted.
I heard it.
I'd rather have a sparkling face tomorrow than be honored
If I don't let myself miss it
Though memories are layered with color and blurred
Somehow in a lovely body
Wanna keep, Tabidachi to itinerary
Well, we've just finished putting in the choreography and making the choreography.
This time, unusually for Juice, there's a rap in the song.
The song starts with a rap song called “Satawa”.
At the beginning, you said, “Yay!
You had me.
I really liked the choreography from the beginning. I really liked the choreography from the beginning.
So it's a choreography that is easy to express nuance.
Each member has a different way of expressing the nuance of the choreography.
If you watch the choreography for 10 people, you will see it at least 10 times.
Then I'll watch Oshio's choreography many times.
I'm sure you'll watch the music video at least 100 times.
The song “Aiko” was written by Tsunku.
It's been a while since Juice has had a Tsunku song, so I'm really happy about it.
I'm really happy about it, but at the same time
At the same time, I wonder what it is...
At the same time, I don't really feel that this will be the last single for Mr. Uemura.
I still don't really feel it yet.
The last part of the choreography...
And there's a part in the chorus where Mr. Uemura does the “fah” sound.
I'm sure that when we perform it live, I'm going to go “aah” like this.
I was smiling when I was choreographing the choreography, but it will come out again when we perform it live.
I thought it would be a great song at the live performance.
It's been a while since JuiceJuice has heard a song by Mr. Tsunku, so I was very happy to hear this song.
When JuiceJuice received the tentative song, Ria Matsunaga was at the same work site as me, and she called me up and asked me if I was interested in the song.
She asked me to listen to it, and it was the first time for me to listen to it.
I heard it for the first time, and after the flamenco, tango, and sexy shuffle of the early Juice, Tsunku's time came to a halt.
After the Tsunku period ended, the next song I heard was Sexy Sexy.
I thought that this was how Juice had changed in TSUNKU's mind.
But this time, I felt that the image of Juice has changed again in TSUNKU's mind.
But the lyrics are still very mature.
I thought it was probably a song about lost love.
I think it's a song about a lost love, and it probably overlaps with the fact that Uemura is leaving.
I wonder if Juice will sing this song again someday in the future for the first time in a long time.
I'm looking forward to seeing how the young girls of today will express themselves in the future when Juice sings this song again for the first time in a long time.
I just learned that the choreography is by Ms. Yoshiko, and I've seen many morning performances with Ms. Yoshiko over Mr. Tsunku, but this is a completely different atmosphere from that.
It's a totally different atmosphere, or rather, I found that it would be like this if it was choreographed to hit the juice juice.
It's true that Morning is always indebted to both the music and the choreography of the two, but it's not like that at all when Morning does it.
I'm sure there will be opportunities to see them perform live in the future, so I'm looking forward to seeing them in person.
I'm sure there will be opportunities to see them perform live in the future, so I'm looking forward to seeing them in person. That's all for this dance lesson with lots of juice juice!
I'm looking forward to seeing it.
me
Juice Juice News Single Owako Nankoku ScionJuice Juice News Single Owako Southern Europe Scion
Let's work together
Here's the next one!
Ocha no Oma: Momo Kitahara's Makeup Lecture
This is Momo Kitahara's makeup lecture!
This time, she's introducing the makeup she's doing at the live!
Let's have a look!
This is Momo Kitahara from Ocha-no-Ma.
Today I'd like to introduce you to the makeup I, Momo Kitahara, usually do at live performances.
It's the makeup class I've been longing for!
Yay!
I'm so happy to finally be able to perform since I've always been watching!
Right now I'm in the process of finishing my base makeup and eyebrows!
Today, I'd like to introduce mainly eye makeup.
I'm going to show you my forehead, which I don't usually show.
I'm going to show you.
First of all, I'd like to introduce the important eye makeup.
I always use this eyeshadow palette.
There are various types of brushes.
Today, I'm going to use these three types of brushes.
First of all, I'm going to use this large brush.
I'm going to take the color here and apply it to the entire eyehall.
When I apply the color, I just apply it roughly.
Then I'm going to apply it as a base so that it sticks out a little bit here.
I'm going to apply this slightly darker pink from the top.
I'm going to draw it from the outer corner of the eye like this.
I think it will blend in with the lashes when I close it up properly.
So I'm going to apply it very thickly at first.
But I'm going to apply it so that it blends in.
Yes, like this.
I want to fill in the crease of the eye with this eyeliner.
I'm going to pull it like this and fill it in like this.
When I lift it up with my curler later, it will disappear a little.
So I'm going to draw it in very firmly so that it blends in later.
I want to move on to the tear troughs.
I have a thin, flat brush that I can use for eyeliner, and I'm going to use a darker color, a mix of pink and brown, and blend it with my hand.
I blended a little bit of this darker color, pink and brown, and blended it out with my hand and wrote it on the tear troughs of my eyes like this.
I'm a little worried about this at first, but I'm going to use a tear trough concealer to blend it in later, so I'm going to draw it boldly. I'm going to draw it boldly because I'm going to blend it with the tear trough concealer later.
I'm going to use a pencil for tear troughs and a pen for drawing shadows.
I drew it here on the edge of the tear ducts, and I'm going to draw it on the tear ducts so that it blends in with the pencil.
If you wonder how far the tear troughs are, you can draw them like this.
I'll draw it where the tear troughs are like this.
If I need more clothes or something, I use a concealer pen like this and draw a little more.
I also use this concealer pen to add a little more.
I use a little bit of leftover eyeshadow from this brush to draw a faint shadow.
I use a little bit of leftover eyeshadow and draw it like this.
I might back-translate the tear troughs in this way.
Today's makeup is for a live performance, so I want to make it look lame, glittery, and puffy, so I usually do that sometimes, but today I used glittery pencil on top of the tear troughs.
I'm going to use a glittery pencil to apply on the tear troughs.
I sometimes apply this to the inner corner of my eyes when I go to a live performance.
I sometimes apply this to the inner corner of my eyes to use as a highlighter.
Sometimes I apply it like this to give a highlight or a luminous look, and then I apply a little bit more with this third brush.
Then I use this third brush to add a little bit of this color to the tear ducts.
I add a little bit of this color to the tear troughs with this third brush.
I use this brush to apply the glittery lame from the eyeshadow to make it sparkle at the concert.
I'm going to put it on like this.
I put it on by hand. It's so shiny. I love lame.
I'm going to move on to the lashes, which are very important.
When it's good, I can really raise my lashes with just this brower, but right now I'm having a really hard time raising my lashes.
But right now I'm in a period where I can't raise my lashes very much.
Today, I'm going to use a hair dryer to warm them up and raise them by force.
It's important to be very careful because it gets too hot!
I'll see you soon.
Then I'm going to raise them in a second.
First of all, I'm going to use a mascara primer.
I'm going to blend the mascara base with the mascara fibers.
I'm just going to move it up and up and up.
I'm going to use this mascara
I'm going to use this mascara.
Next, I'm going to use tweezers to neatly adjust the mascara.
I've applied it roughly now, so I'm going to use tweezers.
I want to make it look like a bundle.
Yes, I'll do that.
I'm going to use a hot brower to give it a nice shape.
I'm going to adjust the direction. We'll adjust the direction of the lashes.
When your eyelashes are up, it makes a big difference in the way your face looks.
Next, I'd like to work on my lower lashes, which are my charm point.
Apply eyelash primer.
Apply the lash base under the lashes.
I'm going to use this pencil and this line.
This pencil and this line go together.
It's super convenient.
I haven't used the pen one yet.
I'm going to add a little bit of this.
I'm going to add this to the tear ducts.
It's pretty thick.
I'll try my best to make it thinner.
Smile.
Blur a little bit with your finger.
I want to apply mascara to the lower lashes.
Don't apply too much.
The key is to not apply too much.
When I'm performing, I'm going to apply the lower lashes a lot, but when I'm going about my daily life, I want to make it look natural, so I'm going to use a primer.
When I don't apply the lower lash line, or when I'm just using this primer, I'll just apply the eyeliner.
I always make mistakes when I apply eyeliner.
When I make a mistake, I use this disposable cotton swab, a little thinner than a cotton swab.
When I make a mistake, I use this disposable cotton swab, which is a little thinner than a cotton swab, and if I make a mistake, I can use this to adjust the line and it looks really beautiful.
I'm probably going to make a mistake now, so I'm going to use my intuition and pull it out one time.
I'm going to go with my intuition once I've drawn it.
I might be using eyeliner every day for about 15 minutes, really realistically.
Now that the eyeliner is done, the eye makeup is almost done.
I'd like to start finishing the face.
For the blush, this eyeshadow is really good.
I'm using this as a blush.
I use this blush brush, and I take a blush brush, and I put a blush brush, and then I put a blush brush, and then I put a blush brush, and then I put a blush brush.
I'm going to put a lot of this under my eyes.
And then a little bit...
I'll put a little bit on my chin and my nose.
I'm shading. I'm shading the nose.
I'm doing the nose. I'm going to use this.
I've recently started doing shading, and I want to make the tip of my nose look shapely, so I'm using this.
I mix the lighter and darker shades here.
I do it a little bit.
It's like, “Can I see it?
I'm going to put a little bit of shadow.
It's kind of rounded.
So that it looks round.
I put a shadow.
Highlight
I really like this one.
I'm going to use it.
It's also pink and luminous.
The first thing I want to do with the highlighter is to put it right here
Between the eyes
And then on the nose.
Yeah.
And then on the chin.
2 and then use the blush brush.
And then use the blush brush here.
And then a little bit of a glow.
I'd love to have a little bit of a glow.
I'm going to put on my favorite lamé before lipstick.
It's really sparkly, so I put it on for live performances, and it's still sparkly, but it's a little bit bigger.
But it's a little big, so I'm going to put it on a little exaggeratedly first.
Look at this lame!
Now I'm going to put on the lipstick, which has a little plumper effect.
I'm going to apply it.
And I love lipsticks so much that I have a lot of them, but today I've brought three kinds of lipsticks, and I'm going to apply this lipstick as a base.
And then I'm going to put this really dark lip on the inside.
I'm done! Yay!
I think the key point this time is the lame.
Since today's makeup was for a live performance
I used a lot of different kinds of lame.
I'm really trying out different kinds of makeup.
I really love makeup.
I thought it was really interesting and great that makeup is so different for each person.
I'm glad that I was able to participate in this class, and I hope to be able to participate in another makeup class with a different kind of makeup. I am happy to have been able to participate this time, and I hope to be able to participate in another makeup class with a different makeup.
Thank you so much for today!
Bye bye!
I thought Moachan was really amazing.
I've seen your makeup videos on TikTok and so on.
I've seen videos of your makeup on TikTok, but I can't help but think that every single step of the process is so detailed.
You can tell that she really pays attention to every detail.
Personally, I think that even though they put so many things on the tear troughs, the result is very natural.
I personally think that even though they put all these things on the tear troughs, the finished product looks very natural.
The tear troughs appeared so naturally.
That's what I thought was really great.
I don't know, I feel like everyone at the tea ceremony takes a lot of time and energy to put on their makeup.
I had the image that they spend a lot of time and energy on their makeup.
You can tell what's trendy by looking at the tea ceremony.
So, for example, if a tea girl wears dark lipstick...
So, for example, if a tea girl wears dark lipstick, you can tell that dark lipstick is in fashion now.
Or if she wears separate eyelashes...
I would think that the era of Tabacan is over.
I'm sure I'll be thinking about it in the future.
I think this makeup video was a very useful time for me.
That's all for now, this is Momo Tahara's makeup lecture.
Let's watch the rest together!
Sakura Oda of Morning Musume。24 and
and Rio Kitagawa from Morning Musume。 24.
Here's the next one!
Angulum Vivitar Ichigeki Vocal Recording
From Angulum's latest single
Please take a look at the vocal recording by Rikako Sasaki.
How are you doing?
Well...
Goooood.
That's good.
Shoes, shoes.
Okay, let's go to Emre first.
Yes, please.
Good morning.
Good morning. Good morning. - Good morning.
Good morning
Good morning.
You're a picture of hurt, not a single tear, not for free, not a king.
A storm strikes, and in your imagination, you will not be deprived of my value.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. That's totally fine for the part where you run away with the sound.
You can try singing it like that.
Storming, storming, out of my imagination, somewhere around here.
Well, yeah, it's the highest part of a footstep like that, but it's probably not impossible to get out of it.
I think this is a place where you can go all out, so I'm hoping to go all out in areas A and B. The way you get hurt is picturesque.
A single tear is not free, it's not a king.
I'm not a king, I'm not a king, I'm not a king.
Yeah, ok ok ok.
Okay, let's move on to the next one.
Storm, you can't take away the best part of my imagination, my eye strike.
I'm not gonna let you take it away from me, my eye strike
But I'll keep it vertical and push forward. Don't worry.
See you later. I'm going now.
I'll see you later I wish this “see you later” and “see you later” sounded the same when they were cut off
I'll never let you take it away from me.
I won't let you take away my value
I'm not going to let you take it away from me.
But I'll use it as a shield, and I'll keep pushing forward
I'll be fine.
I'll see you later. Are we done?
Yes, yes...
Let's go further to the end.
For the first time in seven years, we'd like you to see it through to the end.
Let's see if we can get the diamonds to glow.
Let's try one.
Yes, sir.
Give him a big, fat blow.
Make him go crazy with love and knives.
I've never seen anything like this.
When it's carved, the tires will glow. Tires glow when they're carved.
It's the first time I've ever seen anything like this, and it's going to be pretty high up at the end.
Especially at the beginning of the first time like this, it's pretty high.
Now say it in falsetto, it's pretty hard to sing here, isn't it?
It's really hard.
I'll leave a little cone sound for the first time and watch until the end, and see if I can do it with my real voice.
Is the sound the same?
Yes, they are different.
The cone is higher.
Yes, it is.
So, yes, it's the same,
Let's leave it at that for the first time like this.
If you watch to the end and it gets engraved, the diamonds will shine. Let's just do this one.
Then, I'm sorry, I'll just do one more from the head.
And I'll say, “Come again only for the first time like this.
Yes, sir.
And I'll go up to Yamato Hikaru.
If he gets scared, give him a blow.
Make him go crazy with love and knives.
Watch me till the end
When it's carved, the diamonds will glow.
Yes, sir.
OK, OK, let's go on to the next one
One after the other, they keep coming, I'm gonna keep going till I love you
I don't have to hit this yet at this point
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
me
I'm just going to server the next wave of tidbits that come my way and I'm going to get over it.
Well, I'm not going to be shy, I'm going to do what you want me to do
Don't be scared, I love you
Okay, well, then it's me who's going to get what I want
Don't be scared.
Let's leave the “I love you” part out of it for a minute.
Okay, okay.
Okay, okay, okay, I've got the brains.
Yes.
I don't mind if the Every Way part is pretty emo, though. I don't mind if the Every Moment part is pretty emo.
Tsuritsu no Neck is Crazy, Brilliantly Raised Every Moment.
Oh, but the image is like that.
Every Moment!
Yes!
Whether the beauty that penetrates is dark or not,
Be beautiful,
Every Moment!
OK!
Thank you!
That's all!
Thank you very much!
The video showed a lot of the best parts of Rikako Sasaki, didn't it?
Rikako has already graduated from Halo Project.
But she performed this song at Yokohama Arena when she graduated.
festival where she performed it for the first time.
And the same day, MonuSuMeist 4 was held.
I thought it was very innovative to perform a new song for the first time at a festival.
I still think it's a song that requires a lot of energy to perform.
The choreography was so intense.
It seems like it would be hard work just to sing the song.
And to perform it at a festival with choreography
After this
Beast of Love
The Beast of Love.
I had already seen Angelem's performance there.
This song is full of Ange's character, and I look forward to seeing how it will continue to evolve in the future.
I am looking forward to seeing how the song will evolve in the future.
I thought it might be a little difficult if I were to perform it myself.
It was so difficult that I thought it might be tough. The choreography was intense as well as the song itself.
So I am really looking forward to performing it a lot in the future.
This is the vocal recording of Rikako Sasaki for “Angellum Vivitar Ichigeki.
Angellum Vivitar Ichigeki
Now on sale
Thanks for watching.
Sakura Oda and Rio Kitagawa are here. Sakura Oda and Rio Kitagawa have brought you
It's time to say goodbye to Upkami!
I've watched a lot of videos this time, and I thought Momo Kitahara's makeup lecture was really wonderful. I think makeup really reveals a person's personality, their particularity and character.
I was really happy to see Momo's careful character and the attention to detail she puts into her makeup.
I, Sakura Oda, took a dance lesson with JuiceJuice's Aiko.
Yoshiko and Tsunku are two of the most famous Morning Musume。 I've been watching the video since I saw Risa Mao's dance lesson.
I was thinking that if Rio and Morning Musume。 I thought, “If I were Rio and Morning Musume。
We talked about how Morning Musume would have choreographed the intro and danced the chorus like this, even though we were the same person.
I thought it would be different if another group sang the same song but could do the same thing as the provider.
I think it's really professional and wonderful that you can write a song that fits the song so well that it would be different if another group sang it.
I thought it was really professional and wonderful.
In this issue of APKAMI, we will take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UPFRONT Group.
Please subscribe to our channel and we'll be showing you things that we don't usually show you.
This time on Apkami, we'll be talking with Sakura Oda of Morning Musume。 24 and
Rio Kitagawa of Morning Musume。 24.
Good bye!
Next time on Apkami
Dance lesson of Younes High to Diamond
and the recording of “Juice Nai Mono Love”!
Please look forward to it!
Thank you for watching!